Blair and Lee Family Papers, 1640-1946 (bulk 1812-1920 ): Finding Aid C0614
Manuscripts Division
- Papers of Blair Lee, 1740-1946; 1857-1925; 218 boxes (1 partial)
  - Papers of Others, 1783 April 13-1924; 21 boxes
    - Miscellaneous, 1783 April 13-1918; 1 box 27 folders
      - Family, 1783 April 13-1917; 18 folders
        - Lee, Anne Clymer Brooke (d. 1903), 1896-1903; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 15)
          Includes AL, 1896; ACS, 1903, to Arthur Lee; 2 Cs, 1903, to Arthur Lee.
        - Lee, Richard Henry (1732-1794): memorandum of agreement between Lee and Henry Lee, Jr, 1783 April 13; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 16)
        - McKim, Anne Brooke, 1903-1913; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 17)
          Includes TLS, 1907, by Henry Ferguson; TLS, 1913, by W. W. H. Wilmer; 2 ACsS, 1903, by Anne B. Lee; 2 receipts.
        - McKim, Randolph H. (1842-1920): printed matter, 1895; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 18)
        - Robinson, Alexander Galt: ALS, 1879, to Frances Ann Lee, 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 19)
      - Others, 1817-1918; 1 box 9 folders
        - J. Robert Daniels: Sailor's Songs, 1864; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 20)
        - C. H. [Ames] to George E. Hamilton: ALS, 1892; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 21)
        - Wm. Ball to Genl. A. Hunter Marshall: ALS, undated; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 22)
        - L. W. Barringer to Reginald Fendall: ALS, 1884; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 23)
        - Clarence K. Bowie: Notebook-Harvard Law School re contracts, undated; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 24)
        - A. H. Brown to Lucy Dickenson: ALS, 1889; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 25)
        - Louise Clagett: report-Marlborough High School, 1914; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 26)
        - Clemintine Y. Clarke to "Cousin John": ALS, 1899; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 27)
        - W. L. Daniels, 1899; 1 folder (Box 447, Folder 28)
          Includes Jorge Nelken y Waldberg to Mr. Daniels, ALS, 1899; J. A. Graham to Mr. Daniels, 4 ALsS [1899]; Mr. Daniels to Mr. Graham, telegram (copy) [1899]; H. C. Scott to Mr. Daniels, telegram, 1899; Chas. W. Knapp to W. L. Daniels, telegram.
        - W. E. Davis: ledgers, 1915 June-July; 2 folders (Box 448, Folder 1-2)
        - [Sally], G. I. to Mrs. Elisha Biggs: ALS, 1851; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 3)
        - G. Sinclair Gilchrist to G. H. Lindenberger: TLS, 1898; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 4)
        - E. B. Harrison to "Cousin Ran": ALS, undated; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 5)
        - J. [Hatte] to Rev. J. G. Butler: ALS, 1868, regarding Mary E. Jenkins Surratt, 1817-1865; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 6)
        - V. W. Hawkins: Notebook- The Scarlet Letter, undated; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 7)
        - Samuel H. Hoge to M. L. Squires: ALS, 1899; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 8)
        - S. A. King to William Coppinger: ALS, 1887; "Brother Jared" to "My Dear Sister", ALS, 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 9)
        - M. K. Knight to L. C. Hutton: 1 ALS, undated; 1 AMsS, undated, Comments on Mr. Crosby's Criticism, 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 10)
        - J. S. McCeney to "Dear Ed" (E. P. McCeney): ALS, 1887; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 11)
        - E. B. Duval to Charles Moritz, ALS, 1884; Charles Moritz to Reginald Fendall, ALS, 1884; William H. Lukens to Reginald Fendall, ALS, 1885; miscellaneous financial material, 1884-1885; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 12)
        - Kat J. Mulleur to "My Dear Martha": ALS, 1898; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 13)
        - Edward A. Newman to Thomas U. Sisson: TLS (copy), 1914; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 14)
        - Reinhold Niebuhr to Asher E. Hinds, TLS, 1942; James L. Adams to Asher E. Hinds, TLS, 1942; Massey H. Shepherd to Asher E. Hinds, TLS, 1942; Edwin E. Aubrey to Asher E. Hinds, TLS, 1942; copy of Dr. Niebuhr's A Bibliography, undated; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 15)
        - Roger Shaw to "My Dear Major": TLS, 1917; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 16)
        - Bond Smith: Notebook, George Washington University Law School regarding torts, 1908; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 17)
        - Levi L. Todd to Major Thomas P. Moore: ALS, 1837; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 18)
        - Notes of [Woodrow] Wilson's 14 Points, 1918; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 19)
        - "A Roman Catholic Clergyman" Letters to an Enquirer after Truth, 1840; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 20)
        - "A Visitor" to "Gentn": ALS, undated; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 21)
        - [Melissa] to Mrs. H. R. Rathbone: ACS, 1903; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 22)
        - "Clarence" to "Arthur": ALS, 1900; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 23)
        - Miscellaneous Manuscripts, 1880-1881; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 24)
          Includes Reports of Miss Lillie Reddinger of the Cedars School, 1880-1881; Princeton University Debating Committee Accounts; "Notice of the Late Major General Brown" by Major General Jesup; Bartholow's Solid Water-proof Cartridge Report; Police Report; James F. Early.
        - Quotations and Fragments of Writings, undated; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 25)
        - Unidentified, 1834-1917; 1 folder (Box 448, Folder 26)